{
    "subject": "resource/Arnold_Schwarzenegger",
    "predicate": "ontology/successor",
    "object": "resource/Jerry_Brown",
    "human_readable": "Arnold Schwarzenegger was succeeded by Jerry Brown.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9684251546859741,
            "question": "What position did Jerry Brown hold after succeeding Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9148212671279907,
            "question": "Are there any notable events that occurred during Jerry Brown's governorship after succeeding Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620028853416443,
            "question": "What year did Jerry Brown become governor after Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7511208653450012,
            "question": "Did Jerry Brown previously hold the position of governor before Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231830954551697,
            "question": "Was Arnold Schwarzenegger succeeded by a different political party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6214568018913269,
            "question": "What were the political affiliations of both Arnold Schwarzenegger and Jerry Brown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6185836791992188,
            "question": "Who succeeded Arnold Schwarzenegger as governor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5698944330215454,
            "question": "How did the public react to the transition from Arnold Schwarzenegger to Jerry Brown as governor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4445146322250366,
            "question": "What are some key differences in policies between Arnold Schwarzenegger and Jerry Brown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2925706207752228,
            "question": "Who served as governor before Jerry Brown?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arnold Schwarzenegger was succeeded by Jerry Brown.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7997_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key differences in policies between Arnold Schwarzenegger and Jerry Brown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7997_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the public react to the transition from Arnold Schwarzenegger to Jerry Brown as governor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7997_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who succeeded Arnold Schwarzenegger as governor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7997_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7997_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that Arnold Schwarzenegger was succeeded as governor of California by Jerry Brown. Therefore, the statement \"Arnold Schwarzenegger was succeeded by Jerry Brown\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}